console.log("In Populate Db");

import {Meteor} from 'meteor/meteor'
import {Mongo} from 'meteor/mongo'
import {cQA} from '/imports/api/collections/QA/QA'

// db.QA.find({ $and : [ { $or : [ { strDifficulty : "easy" } ] },  { strQuestion : { $exists : true } }, { arrCategories : { "$in" : ["mathamatics"] } }  ]}).count();
// db.QA.find({ $and : [ { $or : [ { strDifficulty : "intermediate" } ] },  { strQuestion : { $exists : true } }, { arrCategories : { "$in" : ["mathamatics"] } }  ]}).count();
// db.QA.find({ $and : [ { $or : [ { strDifficulty : "advanced" } ] },  { strQuestion : { $exists : true } }, { arrCategories : { "$in" : ["mathamatics"] } }  ]}).count();

// let arrData = [
// 	{ "_id" : "bYhEZbFJo2ymLHuJY", "strQuestion" : "1 + 3 - 4 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "physics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-20T06:47:40.255Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "ET7MzmSrACRxEbTzW", "strQuestion" : "3 * 3 - 5 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:21:22.125Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "5ik8Nv8ef6A7oywys", "strQuestion" : "21 - 17 + 12 - 21 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:23:19.736Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-5", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "52", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "-21", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "-7", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "pE2fqnZWo54Kvxmbm", "strQuestion" : "33 * 10 + 27 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:24:23.675Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "327", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "317", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "357", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "332", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "ypgjDterWjKw4oz3b", "strQuestion" : "28 * 5 - 14 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:26:06.556Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "126", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "140", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "154", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "124", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "BX5v7WH66798c7Fa2", "strQuestion" : "44 * 2 + 33 / 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:27:31.933Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "82", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "94", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "40", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "m9uGc6Xy4XiZSxRxM", "strQuestion" : "12 - 5 + 6 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:03:20.532Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "9x58kHWEpvupBSvzM", "strQuestion" : "17 + 12 - 13 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:04:29.476Z")},
// 	{ "_id" : "L7ARq2TjBiTFAuqst", "strQuestion" : "7 * 7 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "53", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "63", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:06:10.745Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "Y9F3mN2NqYNuGZoNs", "strQuestion" : "8 - 26 + 5 +26 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T23:41:40.238Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "F4Z8su77bSTFvmbok", "strQuestion" : "11 + 3 * 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "28", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "17", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "26", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "19", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:09:17.115Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "Ry9aceiqixZsp9qDM", "strQuestion" : "6 + 6 / 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:10:38.895Z") }
// ];

// let arrData = [
// 	{ "_id" : "bYhEZbFJo2ymLHuJY", "strQuestion" : "1 + 3 - 4 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "physics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-20T06:47:40.255Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "ET7MzmSrACRxEbTzW", "strQuestion" : "3 * 3 - 5 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:21:22.125Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "5ik8Nv8ef6A7oywys", "strQuestion" : "21 - 17 + 12 - 21 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:23:19.736Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-5", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "52", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "-21", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "-7", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "pE2fqnZWo54Kvxmbm", "strQuestion" : "33 * 10 + 27 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:24:23.675Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "327", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "317", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "357", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "332", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "ypgjDterWjKw4oz3b", "strQuestion" : "28 * 5 - 14 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:26:06.556Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "126", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "140", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "154", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "124", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "BX5v7WH66798c7Fa2", "strQuestion" : "44 * 2 + 33 / 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:27:31.933Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "82", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "94", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "40", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] },
// 	{ "_id" : "m9uGc6Xy4XiZSxRxM", "strQuestion" : "12 - 5 + 6 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:03:20.532Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "9x58kHWEpvupBSvzM", "strQuestion" : "17 + 12 - 13 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:04:29.476Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "L7ARq2TjBiTFAuqst", "strQuestion" : "7 * 7 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "53", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "63", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:06:10.745Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "Y9F3mN2NqYNuGZoNs", "strQuestion" : "8 - 26 + 5 +26 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T23:41:40.238Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "F4Z8su77bSTFvmbok", "strQuestion" : "11 + 3 * 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "28", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "17", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "26", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "19", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:09:17.115Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "Ry9aceiqixZsp9qDM", "strQuestion" : "6 + 6 / 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:10:38.895Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "xYZc9YRNkDb896mBZ", "strQuestion" : "(3/4 + 5/4) + 12 - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:37:12.563Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "SkimDy7eqgb3y7zmQ", "strQuestion" : "2 * ( 3 + 7 ) - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "18", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:38:33.947Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "ojfGXPFmMfJWK59aj", "strQuestion" : "3 + 3 * 12 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "108", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "72", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:40:19.449Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "fZ7FLxvTpeNZxmXPK", "strQuestion" : "77/77 + 44/22 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "77", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "44", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:43:12.261Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "hwAeW2KuhofAReH8p", "strQuestion" : "7 - 2 * 4 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-1", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "20", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:44:30.663Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "622W64pqNNyYLktdg", "strQuestion" : "24 / 12 + 6 / 12 + 6 / 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "advanced", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:46:57.718Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "dBk4becJjuKNjD4gb", "strQuestion" : "36 / 6 + 81 / 9 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "advanced", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "45", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:48:09.446Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "qbC6Gc7GAjNTP7xuH", "strQuestion" : "52+7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "57", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "60", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "59", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "61", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:03:20.166Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "HsBubooAb4hfnEbPK", "strQuestion" : "7 + 9 - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "14", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "18", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:05:03.216Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "wBS4yfFf6y7CfYyLs", "strQuestion" : "24/12 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:06:26.541Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "DPdciRPdHvd2r96ks", "strQuestion" : "2 * 2 * 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "10", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:07:33.348Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "pB5AHtGC6YkAC5maK", "strQuestion" : "4 * 4 / 4 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:08:50.237Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "8iHD64jXJxMf5oLyW", "strQuestion" : "(5 * 6 ) * 1 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "29", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "30", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "31", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:09:54.259Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "TTzLE7JSBhRyK2W5c", "strQuestion" : "12 + 33 + 4 - 33 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "43", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "49", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:10:31.787Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "cJ7sHWqwoZeNH3euY", "strQuestion" : "32 * 1 - 32 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-1", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "1", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "0", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "32", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:11:24.555Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "ro5huAMxKPzjGPWsz", "strQuestion" : "16 / 4 + 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:16:49.256Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "tb9yuYWb3j7JgeAYB", "strQuestion" : "10 * 10 - 10 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "90", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "110", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "101", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:13:28.212Z") },
// 	{ "_id" : "qPZKw39dkYFRLvofE", "strQuestion" : "9 * 9 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "81", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "90", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "72", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:14:10.546Z") }
// ]

// ,{ "_id" : "xYZc9YRNkDb896mBZ", "strQuestion" : "(3/4 + 5/4) + 12 - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:37:12.563Z") }
// 	,{ "_id" : "SkimDy7eqgb3y7zmQ", "strQuestion" : "2 * ( 3 + 7 ) - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "18", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:38:33.947Z") }
// 	,{ "_id" : "pE2fqnZWo54Kvxmbm", "strQuestion" : "33 * 10 + 27 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:24:23.675Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "327", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "317", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "357", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "332", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
// 	,{ "_id" : "ypgjDterWjKw4oz3b", "strQuestion" : "28 * 5 - 14 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:26:06.556Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "126", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "140", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "154", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "124", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
// 	,{ "_id" : "BX5v7WH66798c7Fa2", "strQuestion" : "44 * 2 + 33 / 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-06T14:11:45.611Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "82", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "94", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "40", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
// 	,{ "_id" : "m9uGc6Xy4XiZSxRxM", "strQuestion" : "12 - 5 + 6 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:03:20.532Z") }
// 	,{ "_id" : "ojfGXPFmMfJWK59aj", "strQuestion" : "3 + 3 * 12 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "108", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "72", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:40:19.449Z") }
// 	,{ "_id" : "fZ7FLxvTpeNZxmXPK", "strQuestion" : "77/77 + 44/22 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "77", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "44", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:43:12.261Z") }
// 	,{ "_id" : "cn69DNSTs39ntPMzG", "strQuestion" : "34 - 7 + 8 - 34 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "27", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T12:59:28.127Z") }
// 	,{ "_id" : "hKdN7NJSj4bXg7jb4", "strQuestion" : "6 + 5 + 4 + 3 + 2 + 1 + 0 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "21", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "19", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "26", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:11:51.365Z") }

let arrData = [
	{ "_id" : "bYhEZbFJo2ymLHuJY", "strQuestion" : "1 + 3 - 4 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-20T06:47:40.255Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
	,{ "_id" : "ET7MzmSrACRxEbTzW", "strQuestion" : "3 * 3 - 5 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:21:22.125Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
	,{ "_id" : "5ik8Nv8ef6A7oywys", "strQuestion" : "21 - 17 + 12 - 21 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-11-26T05:23:19.736Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-5", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "52", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "-21", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "-7", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
	,{ "_id" : "9x58kHWEpvupBSvzM", "strQuestion" : "17 + 12 - 13 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:04:29.476Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "L7ARq2TjBiTFAuqst", "strQuestion" : "7 * 7 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "53", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "63", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:06:10.745Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "Y9F3mN2NqYNuGZoNs", "strQuestion" : "8 - 26 + 5 +26 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T23:41:40.238Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "F4Z8su77bSTFvmbok", "strQuestion" : "11 + 3 * 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "28", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "17", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "26", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "19", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:09:17.115Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "Ry9aceiqixZsp9qDM", "strQuestion" : "6 + 6 / 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "11", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2015-12-26T18:10:38.895Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "qbC6Gc7GAjNTP7xuH", "strQuestion" : "52+7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "57", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "60", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "59", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "61", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:03:20.166Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "HsBubooAb4hfnEbPK", "strQuestion" : "7 + 9 - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "14", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "18", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:05:03.216Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "wBS4yfFf6y7CfYyLs", "strQuestion" : "24/12 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:06:26.541Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "DPdciRPdHvd2r96ks", "strQuestion" : "2 * 2 * 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "10", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:07:33.348Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "pB5AHtGC6YkAC5maK", "strQuestion" : "4 * 4 / 4 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:08:50.237Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "8iHD64jXJxMf5oLyW", "strQuestion" : "(5 * 6 ) * 1 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "29", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "30", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "31", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:09:54.259Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "TTzLE7JSBhRyK2W5c", "strQuestion" : "12 + 33 + 4 - 33 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "43", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "49", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:10:31.787Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "cJ7sHWqwoZeNH3euY", "strQuestion" : "32 * 1 - 32 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-1", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "1", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "0", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "32", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:11:24.555Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "ro5huAMxKPzjGPWsz", "strQuestion" : "16 / 4 + 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:16:49.256Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "tb9yuYWb3j7JgeAYB", "strQuestion" : "10 * 10 - 10 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "90", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "110", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "101", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:13:28.212Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "qPZKw39dkYFRLvofE", "strQuestion" : "9 * 9 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "81", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "90", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "72", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T19:14:10.546Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "hwAeW2KuhofAReH8p", "strQuestion" : "7 - 2 * 4 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-1", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "20", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:44:30.663Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "FdYLA6J5LRensKA9A", "strQuestion" : "23 + 16 + 1 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "35", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "40", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "41", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:02:23.935Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "4EiQ2eu8EzNMjDKYc", "strQuestion" : "31 + 11 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "41", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "40", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "43", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:03:01.666Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "rYP3GBBGZg5hKa5Ac", "strQuestion" : "17 - 4 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "17", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "20", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "21", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:04:38.576Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "q7BZXJEWaH2bNzwvf", "strQuestion" : "26 * 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "32", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "48", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "52", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:05:41.346Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "Zno3DR94ddWExiLcY", "strQuestion" : "42 - 8 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "38", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "34", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "32", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:06:41.919Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "B8iANsNWNAB6A493N", "strQuestion" : "38 - 7 + 1 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "30", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "29", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "32", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:08:20.986Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "rvDXzPGjxJKC5WqtM", "strQuestion" : "3 + 3 * 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "18", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "9", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:09:17.653Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "xrZ7AYsm5497deYfL", "strQuestion" : "3 * 2 * 1 * 0 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "0", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:13:33.146Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "JhRNMBDQLnsxaK8wS", "strQuestion" : "3 + 2 + 1 + 0 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "0", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:14:53.542Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "kupXjwQhiD68ySJ8J", "strQuestion" : "3 - 2 + 1 + 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:18:39.609Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "5TRQYJkNXvWQguyya", "strQuestion" : "22 - 2 + 19 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "49", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "49", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:20:14.398Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "XCwif4sFnCdtoZCpm", "strQuestion" : "5 + 4 + 2 + 1 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "14", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:21:26.874Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "SWiAvnZa6La6iney3", "strQuestion" : "3 + 4 + 1  = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "9", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:22:59.629Z") }	
	,{ "_id" : "bP4HBHxKSjTd6hNC5", "strQuestion" : "-2 + (-2) - (-4) + 4 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "-2", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "-6", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:24:36.460Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "BPwvXfcWxJ98EdS62", "strQuestion" : "(-3) - (-3) = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "0", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "-3", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "-6", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:25:23.830Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "agQdp4HNo8aczc4Yr", "strQuestion" : "8 * 8 - 60 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "easy", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "10", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:26:55.198Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "hKdN7NJSj4bXg7jb4", "strQuestion" : "6 + 5 + 4 + 3 + 2 + 1 + 0 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "21", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "19", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "26", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.753Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "pE2fqnZWo54Kvxmbm", "strQuestion" : "33 * 10 + 27 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.532Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "327", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "317", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "357", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "332", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
	,{ "_id" : "ypgjDterWjKw4oz3b", "strQuestion" : "28 * 5 - 14 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.537Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "126", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "140", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "154", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "124", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
	,{ "_id" : "BX5v7WH66798c7Fa2", "strQuestion" : "44 * 2 + 33 / 3 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.548Z"), "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "82", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "94", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "99", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "40", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ] }
	,{ "_id" : "xYZc9YRNkDb896mBZ", "strQuestion" : "(3/4 + 5/4) + 12 - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "36", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.592Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "SkimDy7eqgb3y7zmQ", "strQuestion" : "2 * ( 3 + 7 ) - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "18", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.611Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "ojfGXPFmMfJWK59aj", "strQuestion" : "3 + 3 * 12 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "108", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "72", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.617Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "fZ7FLxvTpeNZxmXPK", "strQuestion" : "77/77 + 44/22 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "77", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "44", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "3", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.624Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "cn69DNSTs39ntPMzG", "strQuestion" : "34 - 7 + 8 - 34 + 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "27", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "22", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:13:28.713Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "H4tYXzN3wJnMNJsri", "strQuestion" : "33 + 38 - 1 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "80", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "69", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "79", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "70", "boolIsCorrect" : true } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:47:11.909Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "YBL8SAbsd3yRXSkiC", "strQuestion" : "32 + 52 - 30 - 50 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "30", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "51", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:48:42.637Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "PmxA3RbpzaaPakFN5", "strQuestion" : "30 - 50 + 32 - 52 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-32", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "-48", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "-40", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "-50", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:49:54.967Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "PB98hsPrR4Z8L9Abh", "strQuestion" : "(4 + 3)/2 + 10/4 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:53:30.930Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "xxG4xYHR5rbWaoRvx", "strQuestion" : "( 3 + 3 / 2  ) *  2  = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "6/2", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "9", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "9/2", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:55:16.126Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "CPgAzNEFbWX7C7Wfo", "strQuestion" : "77 - 8 - 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "-10", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "-67", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "67", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "69", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:56:59.466Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "yhF5ATrYKQkpx6xD7", "strQuestion" : "(42 + 7) / ( 9 - 2 ) = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "7", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "8", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "9", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "13", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:58:25.779Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "LJaTgFBfHhdh4tu2e", "strQuestion" : "4 + 6 / 2 - 5 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "5", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "2", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "1", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T19:00:19.981Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "ZE5ziGdiwwnsmn4At", "strQuestion" : "17 * 2 + 13 - 7 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "35", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "31", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "40", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "37", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T19:01:24.084Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "eh4EWuhkdQPbJRPHN", "strQuestion" : "( 14 - 1 ) + 23 * 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "intermediate", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "39", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "49", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "59", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "69", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T19:02:50.710Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "622W64pqNNyYLktdg", "strQuestion" : "24 / 12 + 6 / 12 + 3 / 2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "advanced", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "4", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "6", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-08T15:10:31.311Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "dBk4becJjuKNjD4gb", "strQuestion" : "36 / 6 + 81 / 9 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "advanced", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "56", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "24", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "45", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-05T18:48:09.446Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "6xCudfR7xoKTHCPNp", "strQuestion" : "22 + 22 + 2 = x - 2. \nWhat is the value of x ?", "strDifficulty" : "advanced", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "46", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "48", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "44", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "42", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:01:17.284Z") }
	,{ "_id" : "PfSGiQZ44NqQhxfi6", "strQuestion" : "25 + 5 - 5/2 + 3/2 = ?", "strDifficulty" : "advanced", "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "30", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "29", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "31", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "26", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], "createdAt" : Date("2016-11-03T18:42:29.897Z") }
]

Meteor.startup(function () {
    if (cQA.find().count() === 0) {

    	arrData.forEach((oData,idx) => {
    		cQA.insert(oData);
    	});
    }

    // cQA.update(
    // 	{ "_id" : "PfSGiQZ44NqQhxfi6"}, 
    // 	{
    // 		$set : {"strQuestion" : "25 + 5 - 5/2 + 3/2 = ?"}
    // 	}
    // );

    cQA.update(
    	{ "_id" : "XCwif4sFnCdtoZCpm"}, 
    	{
    		$set : {"arrAnswers" : [ 
    			{ "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, 
    			{ "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "14", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, 
    			{ "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, 
    			{ "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ]}
    	}
    );
    		// $set : {"strQuestion" : "25 + 5 - 5/2 + 3/2 = ?"}

    // { "_id" : "XCwif4sFnCdtoZCpm", 
    // "strQuestion" : "5 + 4 + 2 + 1 = ?", 
    // "strDifficulty" : "easy", 
    // "arrCategories" : [ "mathamatics" ], 
    // "arrAnswers" : [ { "strLabel" : "A", "strValue" : "15", "boolIsCorrect" : false }, { "strLabel" : "B", "strValue" : "14", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "C", "strValue" : "12", "boolIsCorrect" : true }, { "strLabel" : "D", "strValue" : "16", "boolIsCorrect" : false } ], 
    // "createdAt" : Date("2016-10-17T13:21:26.874Z") }

});
